hello and welcome to english learning
hub
[Music]
english listening test
this test consists of 30 questions which
are divided into six parts
i will give you a short instruction at
the beginning of each part
before we get started take a pen and
paper so you can take notes while
listening
are you ready
let's get started
part one
listen to a student talking to the
receptionist of a language school
are you a new student
yes i am
i need to ask you some questions okay
what's your first name alisa
alisa how do you spell that
a l i s a
thanks and what's your surname elisa
bernard
that's b e r n a r d
fine
how old are you
i'm 22.
where are you from
i'm from france from paris the capital
city
what's your address in the u.s
14 ramsey street brooklyn in your zip
code
oh it's 11 222.
what's your phone number
my cell phone
yes please
it's 7 18
718-555-8545
that's great
i'll take you up to your classroom now
your class is in room 7 and your teacher
is robert brown
choose the correct option
[Music]
part two
listen to five conversations and take
notes hello i'm jenny what's your name
luis sanchez are you a new student
no i'm not i'm the new spanish teacher
oh right i'm the english teacher
luis this is the teacher's room come in
and sit down
hi jenny hello arya
arya this is luis sanchez he's the new
spanish teacher nice to meet you luis
nice to meet you arya
arya is the director of the school
are you spanish luis
no i'm from salta in argentina
how do you spell salta
s a l t a
is sultan near buenos aires
no it's in the north of argentina
what's your email address luis oh it's
louise 700 gmail.com
there's a party at my house this weekend
i'll send you my address okay thanks
see you later goodbye
bye see you on monday no i'll see you
tomorrow tomorrow but we aren't at
school tomorrow it's saturday i know but
jenny's party is tomorrow oh yes
see you tomorrow luis
choose the correct option
[Music]
part three
listen to samuel carlos and jack saying
what they have on their table or desk
name's samuel i'm an english teacher i
have a really big desk in my room i have
lots of things on the desk i have a
computer and a printer pens and pencils
a photo of my children an english
dictionary and a big yellow lamp my desk
is very clean
i'm carlos and i'm a student i have a
table in my room it isn't a very big
table but i have a lot of things on it
and it isn't very clean
i have my laptop i also have a big box
of tissues lots of spanish magazines and
the keys to my little blue car
my name's jack
my desk is small at the moment it's
clean on my desk i have my computer a
small red lamp a black file a phone a
pair of scissors and an old calendar
choose the correct option
[Music]
part four
listen to five conversations and take
notes
slow down mark
you're a good driver but this road isn't
very safe
don't worry mom
oh mark
please slow down and be more careful
i'm cold mark
can you turn the air conditioning off
okay mom oh dad i'm really hot now
open your window megan
i'm bored are we there yet
not yet it's about 120 miles
dad i'm hungry
can we stop at that cafe mark
i'm thirsty
okay
give me that music magazine
no this is my magazine
no it isn't yes it is
be quiet you too
tom listen to your ipod
megan read your magazine
turn the radio on mark
we're here at grandma's new house
great
it's a beautiful house grandma
thank you megan
don't park your mark look at that sign
oh dear
choose the correct option
[Music]
part five
emma and sophia meet in a cafe
listen to their conversation
hello monica
hi emma
sorry i'm late
this is my sister sophia
sophia emma is one of the teachers i
work with at the school
nice to meet you sophia
you too emma
sit down you too
what do you want to drink sophia
oh an espresso for me please
another coffee emma
tea for me please
okay
do you live in lowell sofia
no i live in summerville it's a small
town near boston
oh my parents live in boston
they have a computer store downtown
what do you do
me i teach film studies at boston
university
film studies
how interesting
it's an interesting job i watch lots of
movies at work what kind of movies do
you like i don't like modern hollywood
movies i prefer old black and white
british films what about you
i teach french and spanish so i like
foreign films this music is terrible
what kind of music do you like
my friends like heavy metal but i prefer
jazz when i'm in boston i go to a club
called the kingdom they have great jazz
nights
i go there too i love jazz here's monica
with the drinks
here you are
an espresso for you sophia a tea for
emma and a latte for me
great
choose the correct option
[Music]
part six
listen to five speakers and identify the
question they are answering
yes i do
i don't work in an office and i'm never
bored
i travel a lot and i meet interesting
people and the other flight attendants
are really nice
it's a great job and i earn quite a lot
of money
choose the correct option
i study chinese and economics in college
i want to work in china one day
i think it's a really interesting
country
the language is quite difficult to learn
though
i listen to chinese songs in my car to
help with my pronunciation
choose the correct option
yes i do
i'm in a big office with six other
people
they're very nice and we're all friends
after work we often have dinner in a
restaurant or go out for a drink
i think it's important to work with nice
people
choose the correct option
[Music]
i work at home so i don't travel to work
i have an office in my house with a big
desk
i have a computer and a printer in my
office and hundreds of files and books
my office isn't very clean and it's
difficult to find things
choose the correct option
no i don't
i meet my friends on saturdays and we go
shopping or we go to the movies on
sundays i play tennis with my sister
if it rains we stay at home and read the
newspapers
i like my job but i only work monday to
friday
choose the correct option
don't forget to share your score in the
comments section
we will upload more listening tests for
next levels very soon so stay tuned
see you in the next videos
[Music]